<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Datatypes xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" copyright="Copyright (c) FIX Protocol Ltd. All Rights Reserved." edition="2010" version="FIX.4.1" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../schema/Datatypes.xsd" generated="2010-03-13T14:54:02-05:00">
	<Datatype added="FIX.2.7">
		<Name>int</Name>
		<Description>Sequence of digits without commas or decimals and optional sign character (ASCII characters "-" and "0" - "9" ). The sign character utilizes one byte (i.e. positive int is "99999" while negative int is "-99999"). Note that int values may contain leading zeros (e.g. "00023" = "23").
Examples:
723 in field 21 would be mapped int as |21=723|.
-723 in field 12 would be mapped int as |12=-723|
The following data types are based on int.</Description>
	</Datatype>
	<Datatype added="FIX.2.7">
		<Name>float</Name>
		<Description>Sequence of digits with optional decimal point and sign character (ASCII characters "-", "0" - "9" and "."); the absence of the decimal point within the string will be interpreted as the float representation of an integer value. All float fields must accommodate up to fifteen significant digits.</Description>
	</Datatype>
	<Datatype added="FIX.2.7">
		<Name>char</Name>
		<Description>Alpha-numeric free format strings, can include any character or punctuation except the delimiter. All char fields are case sensitive.</Description>
	</Datatype>
	<Datatype added="FIX.4.0">
		<Name>time</Name>
		<Description>Time/date combination in YYYYMMDD-HH:MM:SS format, colons and dash required. Valid values: YYYY = 0000-9999, MM = 01-12, DD = 01-31, HH = 00-23, MM = 00-59, SS = 00-59.</Description>
	</Datatype>
	<Datatype added="FIX.4.0">
		<Name>date</Name>
		<Description>Date in YYYYMMDD format. Valid values: YYYY = 0000-9999, MM = 01-12, DD = 01-31.</Description>
	</Datatype>
	<Datatype added="FIX.2.7">
		<Name>data</Name>
		<Description>Raw data with no format or content restrictions. Data fields are always immediately preceded by a length field. The length field should specify the number of bytes of the value of the data field (up to but not including the terminating SOH). Caution: the value of one of these fields may contain the delimiter (SOH) character. Note that the value specified for this field should be followed by the delimiter (SOH) character as all fields are terminated with an "SOH".</Description>
	</Datatype>
	<Datatype added="FIX.4.1">
		<Name>MonthYear</Name>
		<BaseType>char</BaseType>
		<Description>char field representing month of a year in YYYYMM format. Valid values: YYYY = 0000-9999, MM = 01-12.</Description>
	</Datatype>
	<Datatype added="FIX.4.1">
		<Name>DayOfMonth</Name>
		<BaseType>int</BaseType>
		<Description>int field representing a day during a particular monthy (values 1 to 31).</Description>
	</Datatype>
</Datatypes>